This is her last.
STRAW is a thriller, drama, crime film directed by Tyler Perry.
What will be her last straw?
A devastatingly bad day pushes a hardworking single mother to the
breaking point — and into a shocking act of desperation.
Janiyah Wiltkinson, played by Taraji P. Henson.
Nicole, played by Sherri Shepherd.
Detective Kay Raymond, played by Teyana Taylor.
Benny, played by Sinbad.
Chief Wilson, played by Rockmond Dunbar.
Tessa George, played by Ashley Versher.
Diary of a Wimpy Kid: The Last Straw is a 2025 animated comedy film
based on the 2009 book of the same name by Jeff Kinney.
It is the eighth installment in the Diary of a Wimpy Kid film series, the fourth animated film in the
series, and a direct sequel to Diary of a Wimpy Kid Christmas: Cabin Fever (2023).
It is also the second adaptation of The Last Straw, after elements of the book were
previously adapted into the 2012 live-action film Diary of a Wimpy Kid: Dog Days.
The film was announced in July 2025 alongside its sequel The Getaway
(2026), and was released on Disney+ on December 5, 2025.
It received generally mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of bank manager, arrest,
loss of job, sick child, angry.
The tone is emotional and intense.